bloodytrailers.com 2014-06-30

# The Biggest Collection of Bloody Horror Movie Trailers On The NetPrivacy Policy - Bloody Trailers

**BLOODYTRAILERS.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

 Protecting the privacy of all of our users is an ongoing commitment of BLOODYTRAILERS.COM. This Privacy Policy, which applies to all websites and services provided under the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM names and marks, explains how BLOODYTRAILERS.COM treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you, not otherwise publicly available, that personally identifies you; personal information may include your name, location, e-mail address, birth date, or other identifying information. 

 BLOODYTRAILERS.COM has established registration and sign-in procedures which, in conjunction with this Privacy Policy, help ensure the privacy of information provided to BLOODYTRAILERS.COM by its visitors and members while using BLOODYTRAILERS.COM websites. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM website and services, and not to any other websites you may visit before or after BLOODYTRAILERS.COM. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND WHO IS COLLECTING IT**

When you register to become a Member of a BLOODYTRAILERS.COM website, BLOODYTRAILERS.COM collects certain information such as your first and last name, e-mail address, your country of location, and gender, as well as information about each Member's use of BLOODYTRAILERS.COM features and contributions of content (collectively, "Membership Information"). In addition, we may collect survey responses or other information regarding our users' interests and preferences. 

 BLOODYTRAILERS.COM will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or nonaffiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. 

Some contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that will appear on the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM websites may also be sponsored by other companies. These companies may also seek to collect personal information from you. You can avoid providing your personal information to these companies and sponsors by not participating in these contests, sweepstakes or promotions. In any event, you are encouraged to make yourself familiar with the privacy policy specific to any such event prior to your agreement to participate. 

 Please remember that any personal information voluntarily disclosed by you through e-mail, in public-view personal profiles, public-view uploaded materials, chat rooms, message boards, or intra-site message systems, can be seen and possibly used by others. Displaying personal information in such public fashion via our website or services may have unintended privacy implications for you. We encourage you to always remain aware of this possibility. BLOODYTRAILERS.COM encourages you to use common sense and be cautious about what information you may provide on-line, whether through our websites or elsewhere on the Internet. 

 You acknowledge, consent, and agree that BLOODYTRAILERS.COM may access, preserve, use, and disclose your Membership Information, including content uploaded to or downloaded from BLOODYTRAILERS.COM's websites and services, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: 

(a) enforce the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM Terms of Service;
(b) respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third-parties; 
(c) respond to your customer service requests; 
(d) comply with legal process; and/or 
(e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of BLOODYTRAILERS.COM, its users, or the public. 

**HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

 Our primary goal is to provide members with the most useful and enjoyable experience on the Internet. Our advertisers will never be privy to your Membership Information, unless you permit us to give it to them so that they can provide you with products or services. Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM services, including but not limited to sending notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you. 

 The BLOODYTRAILERS.COM website is constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. Member-use information helps guide such changes and the evolution of our websites. Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding membership usage patterns or interests, so that they too can better serve your needs and preferences, but such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. The collection of usage and interest information allows us to provide a constantly evolving and user-sensitive package of services, products, and features that satisfy member needs, wants and desires but always with the priority of protecting individual member privacy. 

**COOKIES**

 BLOODYTRAILERS.COM places cookies on your computer to retain your individual preferences and improve your user experience on our website, as well as to tell us what features of our sites are most popular. We do not store any personal information in cookies, nor do we use cookies to obtain any personal information from you. 

 Affiliates and advertisers, product and service providers may also use their own cookies when you interact with their sites and you should be aware of this as you do so. 

**NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN**

 We at BLOODYTRAILERS.COM take the online safety of children very seriously. BLOODYTRAILERS.COM website and services are directed to adults. We do not allow children under the age of 14 to obtain User Names, and we do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under 14. 

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

 BLOODYTRAILERS.COM may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our websites. In addition, the date at the top of the Policy will indicate when the Policy has most recently been revised; we encourage you to periodically revisit the Privacy Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. You are responsible for reviewing any revisions to this Policy, and your continued use of the BLOODYTRAILERS.COM websites and services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of the Policy. 

**CONTACTING BLOODYTRAILERS.COM**

 If you have a privacy concern regarding any BLOODYTRAILERS.COM website or this Policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the websites, should write to us by email at CONTACT@BLOODYTRAILERS.COM. Alternatively, we can be reached by telephone at Tel: 905-482-3372 or our postal mail address: 

Attention: Privacy Officer  
A. & S. Network Media Solutions Corp.  
7368 Yonge Street - Suite 309  
Thornhill, Ontario  
L4J 8H9  
Canada
